{"Topic": "Oil and Petroleum", "Subject": "General Knowledge", "Data": [{"Question": "Where was oil discovered for the first time in India?", "op1": "Digboi", "op2": "Numaligarh", "op3": "Bongaigon", "op4": "Barauni", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Bharat Oman Refineries Ltd a joint venture of Bharat Petroleum and Oman Oil operates a refinery at \u2013", "op1": "Bhatinda", "op2": "Panipat", "op3": "Bina", "op4": "Mathura", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "At which place in Tamil Nadu is a refinery located?", "op1": "Manali", "op2": "Thanjavur", "op3": "Srirangam", "op4": "Madurai", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "ONGC operates a refinery in Tatipaka which is located in \u2013", "op1": "Karnataka", "op2": "Gujarat", "op3": "Assam", "op4": "Andhra Pradesh", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which of the following is a subsidiary of ONGC?", "op1": "Bongaigaon Refineries and Petrochemicals Ltd", "op2": "Mangalore Refineries and Petrochemicals Ltd", "op3": "Chennai Petroleum Corporation Limited", "op4": "Kochi Refineries Ltd", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "The world\u2019s largest oil refinery operated by Reliance Petroleum is located at \u2013", "op1": "Jamnagar", "op2": "Koyali", "op3": "Visakhapatnam", "op4": "Mangalore"}, {"Question": "At which of the following places is the largest oil refinery in the public sector located?", "op1": "Haldia", "op2": "Panipat", "op3": "Barauni", "op4": "Kochi", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "In which district of Rajasthan is the Aishwarya Oil Field located?", "op1": "Bikaner", "op2": "Barmer", "op3": "Jaisalmer", "op4": "Udaipur", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which company operates the oil fields in Mangala area in Rajasthan?", "op1": "Cairn India", "op2": "Essar Oil", "op3": "Reliance Petroleum", "op4": "ONGC", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "The refinery at Bhatinda is named after \u2013", "op1": "Guru Gobind Singh", "op2": "Bhagat Singh", "op3": "Guru Nanak", "op4": "Ranjit Singh", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which company owns the most number of oil refineries in India?", "op1": "HPCL", "op2": "IOC", "op3": "BPCL", "op4": "ONGC", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Mumbai high oil field is run by which company?", "op1": "Essar India", "op2": "IOCL", "op3": "HPCL", "op4": "ONGC", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Where is the Rajiv Gandhi Institute of Petroleum Technology located?", "op1": "Amethi", "op2": "Rae Bareily", "op3": "Barauni", "op4": "Panipat", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which oil company has its headquarters in Duliajan, Assam?", "op1": "ONGC", "op2": "Oil India", "op3": "GAIL", "op4": "IOCL", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which oil company is not in the Maharatna list of PSEs?", "op1": "HPCL", "op2": "ONGC", "op3": "IOCL", "op4": "BPCL", "Answer": 2}]}